When Wall Street rigged the game, he changed it.
Dumb Money is a history, comedy, drama film directed by Craig Gillespie.
Vlogger Keith Gill sinks his life savings into
GameStop stock and posts about it.
When social media starts blowing up, so do his life and
the lives of everyone following him.
As a stock tip becomes a movement, everyone gets rich—until the billionaires
fight back, and both sides find their worlds turned upside down.
Keith Gill, played by Paul Dano.
Caroline Gill, played by Shailene Woodley.
Jenny Campbell, played by America Ferrera.
Kevin Gill, played by Pete Davidson.
Gabe Plotkin, played by Seth Rogen.
Riri, played by Myha'la.
Dumb Money is a 2023 American biographical comedy-drama film, directed by Craig
Gillespie and written by Lauren Schuker Blum and Rebecca Angelo.
It is based on the 2021 book The Antisocial Network by Ben Mezrich and
chronicles the GameStop short squeeze of January 2021.
The film features an ensemble cast that includes Paul Dano, Pete Davidson, Vincent D'Onofrio, America
Ferrera, Nick Offerman, Anthony Ramos, Sebastian Stan, Shailene Woodley, and Seth Rogen.
After being filmed in New Jersey from October to November 2022, Dumb Money
premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 8, 2023.
It was released in the United States by Columbia Pictures (through Sony Pictures Releasing) in
select theaters on September 15, 2023, and wide release on September 29, 2023.
It received generally positive reviews from critics
and grossed $20 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of massachusetts, manipulation of the media, based
on true story, securities, stocks and bonds , stock price.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.